

# JONNY ZURITA

Front-end developer - UI/UX designer

## ABOUT ME

have exhaustive buildina experience applications and websites that captivate the user's attention (visit my portfolio website if you want to make sure about it). I extremely am detail-focused, as a result, I am able to build visualy outstanding applications. worker, I strive to learn and be a better developer.

# LANGUAGES



Proficient C2

Basic (currently studying it)

# CONTACT

- Valencia Venezuela
- +58 424 440 7910
- jonnyzurita.netlify.app
- jonnyzuritadev@gmail.com
- zuritajonny

### WORK EXPERIENCE

JZ Investments •

Venezuela 2017 - 2019

Web designer Created the graphic image of a local business and directed the relationship with its clients; presetantion of mock-ups, communication, and negotiations.

Connect R. Dubai - UAE 2020 - 2021

Web developer and UI/UX designer Designed and developed more than 30 websites for a conglomerate of Emirati companies; included research and investigation about the specific Emirate.

Frelance 2021 - 2022 Web applications developer

Developed websites and web aplications for a plane ticket company. Exceeded goals when it came to productivty and performance metrics.

Frelance 2022 -

Translator of documentation Managed the translation process of a software for a tech start-up, involved using photoshop and explaining the operation of the software.

### **EDUCATION**

Course 2017 - 2018

Course 2021 - 2022

College 2018 - 2022 Web programming Centecpro Valencia

React: Hooks, Context, Redux, MERN Udemy - Juan Pablo de la Torre Valdez

System Analysis Instituto Universitario de Tecnología para la Información

## SKILLS

HTML 5 years

CSS 5 years

Javascript 3 years

React 2 years

Redux 1 year

Photoshop 6 years



Product design 1 year



Figma 1 year